Mark Anthony Rathbone

Contact Details

HOME ADDRESS

4 Shale Street

Bilston

Wolverhampton

WV14 0HF

PHONE NUMBER

+447984 682775

EMAIL ADDRESS

MarkAnthonyRathbone@gmail.com

LINKEDIN / GITHUB



Summary

I am a CompTIA A+ Certified IT Technician. I have over 10 years of hobbyist experience with tech troubleshooting and problem solving which I am now looking to turn into a career.

My technical skills cover mobile devices, networking technology, hardware, virtualization, cloud computer, network troubleshooting, the installation and configuration of Operating Systems, security, software troubleshooting and understanding of operation procedures.

In addition I am also currently attending an AWS Training Programme where we are studying Linux, Shell, Networking, Security, Python, and the monitoring, support and application of AWS services in the area of compute, storage and networking, including EC2, S3, IAM, VPC, Lamda, Cloud Formation, RDS and Route 53.

Soft Skills

Communication

Time Management

Teamwork

Growth Mindset

Persistence

Personal Responsibility

Work History

AWS RESTART PROGRAMME TRAINEE, GENERATIONS UK&I

June 2020 - Present

During this programme I am studying a 12 week, full-time, classroom based skills development and training on IT fundamentals such as Linux, and learning Python and Shell. In addition we are also studying AWS, including the monitoring and support of AWS services and how to apply AWS services in the area of compute, storage and networking, including EC2, S3, IAM, VPC, Lamda, Cloud Formation, RDS and Route 53.

And finally we are also being taught some professional skills, improving our verbal and written communication skills, and how to explain technical information and terminology to non-technical end users.

RETAIL STAFF, FAST CAR DIRECT

October 2017 - May 2018

A wide variety of general retail duties including greeting, assisting and serving customers in person and over the telephone, picking and packaging parcels to specification ready for dispatch, cleaning and preparing the shop for customers, ensuring shelves are stocked, creating advertisement posters for promotional offers in photoshop, testing products for defects and Technical Support when the need arises.

CUSTOMER ASSISTANT, MULTIMEDIA INTERNET CAFÉ

August 2009 - October 2017

My duties involved setting up the store before opening, such as ensuring the shelves were stocked and computers were ready for use by the customers. Once the café had opened, serving customers and assisting and troubleshooting any issues they were having using the computers or any problems with the computers themselves.

3D Modeler, Freelance

January 2010 - Present

In addition to the above professional work, I also use my spare time to do commision based 3D Model work. This involves all stages of the requested commision. From liaising with the customer, offering them a price, and working on the model whilst also taking feedback on incomplete work to make sure the final product is as the customer desires.

Education & Certifications

CERTIFICATIONS

2018

CompTIA A+ 220-901 CompTIA A+ 220-902

HEATH PARK BUSINESS & ENTERPRISE COLLEGE

2007 - 2009

GCSE in Mathematics – Grade A

GCSE in English – Grade B

GCSE in Applied Science – Grade B

GCSE in Religious Studies - Grade E

OCR Level 2 National Award in ICT - Pass

BTEC First Certificate in Business Studies – Merit

BTEC First Diploma in Art and Design – Merit